mountwashington.org 2015-03-19

# Mount Washington Observatory | Privacy Policy | Mount Washington Observatory

Mount Washington Observatory has created this Privacy Policy to explain why we collect particular information and how we will protect your personal privacy within our Web site. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the Web site located at the following URLs: [www.MountWashington.org](http://www.mountwashington.org/), [www.SeekThePeak.org](http://www.seekthepeak.org/) and [www.WashburnGallery.org](http://www.washburngallery.org/).

In order to fully understand your rights we encourage you to read this Privacy Policy. Mount Washington Observatory reserves the right at any time and without notice to change this Privacy Policy simply by posting such changes on our Site. Any such change will be effective immediately upon posting.

Because we want to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy, this Privacy Policy notifies you of;

  1. What personally identifiable information of yours is collected through the Site;
  2. Who collects such information;
  3. How such information is used;
  4. With whom your information may be shared;
  5. What choices you have regarding collection, use and distribution of your information;
  6. What kind of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control;
  7. and, How you can correct any inaccuracies in your information.

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to Mount Washington Observatory by sending an email to [info@mountwashington.org](mailto:info@mountwashington.org?subject=Privacy%20Policy).

### What Information We Collect and How We Use That Information:

Our online forms require users to give us contact information that may include name, email address, address, interests, and similar information. We do not request or store sensitive information from our visitors, such as social security numbers or complete credit card numbers. We do not sell any lists nor do we make lists available for use by outside organizations.

### Internet Protocol Address:

We collect an IP address from all visitors to our Site. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. We use IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server, administer our Site, analyze trends, track site usage and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use in order for us to improve the Site. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

### Use of "Cookies":

We use cookies, small files that are sent to your Web browser and stored on your computer's hard drive, to improve your Web site experience. The cookie is used to speed up your access to the Web site and the information you wish to see, but it does not contain any personal information. The majority of Web browsers accept cookies, but your browser should give you options for preventing, accepting, or receiving notice of new cookies. However, please be aware that if you block cookies, some Web site functionality may be lost. 

### Security:

All sensitive information provided to Mount Washington Observatory is transmitted using SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption. SSL is a proven coding system that lets your browser automatically encrypt, or scramble, data before you send it to us. We also protect sensitive information by restricting access to that information to certain qualified employees of Mount Washington Observatory. Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure. While we strive to protect your information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of such information. 

### Other Web Sites:

Our Site contains links to other Web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are entering another Web site for which Mount Washington Observatory has no responsibility. We encourage you to read the privacy statements on all such sites as their policies may be different than ours. 

### Refunds:

Mount Washington Observatory is a non-profit organization, and earns income from charitable gifts, membership dues, program fees, corporate sponsorships and retail sales, among other sources. Refunds of charitable contributions or membership dues are requested very infrequently and are handled on a case by case basis. 

Retail items purchased on our Site may be returned for full refund or exchange within 30 days of purchase when accompanied by your packing slip as the receipt. Send items and the packing slip to the address below. If you would like a refund, please indicate the reason for your return. If you would prefer an exchange, indicate the reason for the exchange and instructions so we'll know how to help you, including the exact name of the item you want, along with the color and size you would like. 

If you do not have a packing slip, indicate the order number on a separate piece of paper. Wrap your package securely and mail to:

Mount Washington Observatory  
Attn: Retail Manager  
2779 White Mountain Highway  
P.O. Box 2310  
North Conway, NH 03860

If you have any questions about your order, please contact us at [(603) 356-2137](tel:6033562137), ext. 202.

### Contacting Mount Washington Observatory:

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Site, you can contact:

Mount Washington Observatory  
P.O. Box 2310  
North Conway, NH 03860
